

Profile

A result-oriented marketing professional with over eight years of experience effectively managing marketing projects from conception to completion. Experienced in preparing and overseeing online and offline marketing campaigns. Seeking to enhance and utilize my skill set for organizational growth

Employment History

Sr. Customer marketing Specialist at Honeywell (Trigent)

April 2023 - Present

- Manage marketing projects from conception to execution, ensuring they are completed on time and within budget in a B2B environment
- Measure and reporting ROI from marketing campaigns
- Working and coordinating with agencies, vendors, and media publications
- Responsible for planning and executing Product marketing campaigns for demand generation
- Responsible for creating and developing marketing assets and supporting the sales team
- Collaborate with the internal and external stockholders that are involved in the product development and management
- Plan and execute marketing campaigns to reach target customers.
 This could involve digital and offline channels such as email marketing, social media, trade shows, and events
- Ensure all marketing activities adhere to relevant laws, regulations, and ethical standards.
- Have experience in using tools like SFDC, Tableau, Yammer, Work front, etc

Digital Marketing Executive at TruckNet Digital Technologies, Bangalore

September 2021 — March 2023

- Conduct trials and A/B testing of marketing channels such as paid acquisition, social media, and content creation.
- Create email marketing campaigns with an open rate of over 60% by leveraging tools like mail chimp.
- Plan and execute SEO, database marketing, and social media advertising campaigns.

Digital Marketing Executive at Vikreed Solutions

October 2020 — April 2021

- Planned and assisted the team in developing marketing strategies
- Managed the social media platforms and brand presence across LinkedIn

Details

Bangalore India 6309480278 vasavikbm@gmail.com

Skills

Campaign Management

Integrated Marketing Planning

Digital Marketing Strategy

Campaign Management

Marketing Associate at CDO, New Cairo

December 2013 — March 2016

- Planned and implemented promotional activities and lead-generation campaigns through digital marketing tools
- Masterminded highly successful digital strategies for various platforms to attract customer engagement
- Worked on developing new services and marketing plans by studying industry trends and market research
- Forecasted marketing trends based on previous data to adjust campaigns and maximize results.

Marketing Executive at Vimal interiors Private Limited, Hyderabad

July 2011 — September 2013

- Built brand awareness and generated leads while managing internal and external marketing campaigns and programs
- Created high-quality marketing strategy documentation, including product marketing briefs, FAQs, and objection-handling documents
- Managed relationships with key industry partners and implemented promotional initiatives to maximize marketing program performance

Business Development Executive at Reliance Life Sciences, Hyderabad

June 2010 — June 2011

Collaborated with sales and marketing departments to support client acquisition for pharmaceutical products.

Education

Digital Marketing & Analytics, Indian School Of Business, ISB 2022 – 2022

PGDM _ Marketing , Siva Sivani Institute Of Management Studies , Hyderabad

June 2008 — April 2010

B Sc Biotechnology, S V University

June 2005 — April 2008